A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Audiovisual materials FA752
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation Audio, 1954 - 1980; 3; 130 Reels Audio
  - Judge Leon Higginbotham, 1978 June 21; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4, Reel AV 15387)
  - Second Meeting - Alternative Careers for Ph.D.s in the Humanities, 1974 October 11; Sound, 3 hours 33 minutes; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4, Reel AV 15389)
    Second of two meetings on the subject, organized by D. Lydia Bronte.
  - Program and Policy Underdeveloped Areas Center Studies, 1980 April 7; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4, Reel AV 15390)
  - Program and Policy Underdeveloped Areas Center Studies, 1980 April 7; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4, Reel AV 15391)